Contact

bstefansen11@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/blakestefansen (LinkedIn) bstefansen.github.io/Portfolio/ (Portfolio) github.com/bstefansen (Other)

Top Skills

Geographic Information Systems (GIS)

JavaScript

React.js

Certifications

Responsive Web Design JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Front End Libraries

APIs and Microservices

40-hour OSHA HAZWOPER Online

Honors-Awards

Honors Graduate

Charles L. Blount Scholarship

Florida Bright Futures Scholarship

Florida Credit Union Scholarship

The Education Foundation Senior Scholarship

Blake Stefansen

MERN // Full Stack Developer

Gainesville, Florida

Summary

I'm presently a senior at The University of Florida achieving a bachelor's in geology and certificate in GIS. I also have experience in software development with skills in Javascript, React.js, and Python.

Take a look at my portfolio, and let's get in touch! https://bstefansen.github.io/Portfolio/

Experience

TERRA-COM Environmental Consulting, Inc.

Associate Field Geologist

May 2019 - June 2019 (2 months)

Collaborated with geologists in preparation of site assessments, data evaluation, HASP's, and report writing. Executed groundwater sampling field services compliant with FDEP regulations.

Florida Credit Union

Office Assistant

January 2016 - April 2019 (3 years 4 months)

Gainesville, Florida

Launched first annual cost analysis report of office supplies, informing senior management of decisions for optimizing annual savings. Developed and managed ordering systems for company supplies, streamlining ordering procedures for company branches and departments. Reduced vendor pricing of office supplies. Drafted and optimized procedures for diverse office tasks. Supervised inventory of corporate office to enhance workflow for office personnel.

Walgreens

Customer Service Representative

October 2015 - December 2015 (3 months)

Managed the front register and interacted with customers. Responsibilities included maintaining receipts, answering incoming phone requests, giving appropriate change, requesting price checks, and ringing up sales.

Education

University of Florida

Certificate, Geospatial Information Analysis (GIS) · (2019 - 2020)

University of Florida

Bachelor's degree, Geology · (2018 - 2020)

Santa Fe College

Associate of Arts - AA, Geology · (2017 - 2018)